准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
章鱼费拉图
编剧
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
指导总监
动画总监
分镜指导
统筹
监制
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
偷吃我秋海棠是吧
Biting my begonias, eh?
有我在就休想
Not on my watch
邮件
邮递员
Mailman
什么
Wha--?
是信啊
A letter
谢谢
Thank you
诺斯费拉图
Nosferatu?
什么
What?
又误收到他的邮件了
I got his mail by mistake again
就存到这里面好了
I'll just file that in here
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob?
你躲我垃圾堆里干什么
What are you doing in my garbage?
春季大扫除
Spring cleaning
不过章鱼哥  你这样很可耻
But, Squidward, for shame
不能随便乱丢诺斯费拉图的邮件
You can't just throw out the mail of Nosferatu
必须亲手送到人家手里
You have to deliver it yourself
不然就犯法了
Otherwise, it'd be a federal crime
我也就变成你从犯了
And I'll be an accessory
差不多得了
All right, already
送就送
I'll take it to him
万岁
Hurray
不过邮件得让你带
But you are carrying the mail
才一封信
One little letter?
没问题
No problemo
先等下
Hold on
还有不少
There's more
这些都是他另外的邮件
Here's the rest of it
我误收那怪人的邮件已经有好几年了
I have been getting
that creepy guy's mail by mistake for years
章鱼哥你看
Squidward, look
吸血鬼文摘
"Bleeder's Digest"
精致蝙蝠
"Bat Fancy"
按月订购的鲜血
"Blood of the Month Club"
章鱼哥  知道这代表什么吗
Squidward, do you know what this means?
不知道
No
代表有人收到邮件就会非常开心
It means somebody is going to be very happy
to get all their mail
这个人就是
somebody named
诺斯费拉图
Nosferatu
什么
What?
什么动静
What was that?
别盯着我看了
Stop looking at me
邮件
地图
这里就是收件地址了
Well, this is the address
古堡好高啊
That castle is so high
算我求你们了
Please, I beg you
千万别去古堡
do not go to the castle
堡主是吸血鬼
The master is a vampire
会吸光你的血
He means to suck your blood
你说的都什么东西
What are you talking about?
诺斯费拉图
Nosferatu
对
Right
真抱歉
I'm sorry
我身上没零钱
I don't have any spare change
千万别去古堡
Don't go to the castle
千万别去
Don't go--
去古堡的马车
Well, a coach to the castle
太优雅了
How elegant
快走吧  海绵宝宝
Step lively, SpongeBob
古堡
The castle
看来有人得吃个蟹黄堡了
Looks like someone could use a Krabby Patty
回程坐公交车  不坐马车了
We're taking the bus on the way home
在吗  诺斯费拉图
Hello, Nosferatu?
看来人不在
Well, looks like nobody's home
果然
Of course
在吗
Hello?
我们是来这送你邮件的
We're just here to drop off your mail
怎么回事
What's happening?
原来是诺斯费拉图
It's just Nosferatu
主人向你们表示欢迎
The master bids you welcome
并且感谢你们来送邮件
and he thanks you for dropping off his mail
别闹了
Knock it off
对不起  主人
I am sorry, Master
以后不会再犯了
It won't happen again
我们这就走
We'll let ourselves out
我还不想走
I don't want to leave
天气太恶劣  你们现在走不了
You can't leave due to inclement weather
我们走不了了
We can't leave yet
咽口水
Gulp
主人邀请你们在这过夜
The Master has invited you to stay for the night
不过他想先与你们共进晚餐
but first, he would like to have you both for dinner
那个
Well, uh
现在这种情况吧
under the circumstances
我不介意来点特兰西瓦尼亚美食
I wouldn't mind some fine Transylvanian cuisine
[ 特兰西瓦尼亚：传说中的吸血鬼故乡 ]
换换口味
for a change
零 钱
零钱
Change?
我可以换零钱
I can make change
给我走开
Get away from me
来  来
Come, come
精致蝙蝠
好丰盛
What a spread
不知道要先尝哪个了
I don't know what to try first
我来帮你挑
I can help you decide
我们有烤狼人牙
We have roasted werewolf teeth
腌恶魔胡须
pickled demon beards
炸木乃伊手指
fried mummy fingers
还有鞑靼大脑
and brains tartare
我就不客气开吃了
Don't mind if I do--
也许你们想要点邪恶多汁佳肴
Or maybe you would like something sinfully succulent
喀尔巴阡起司球
A Carpathian cheese ball
[ 特兰西瓦尼亚位于东喀尔巴阡山以西 ]
那是我的饭
That's my dinner
快来爸爸这儿
Come to daddy
一定得来尝尝木乃伊手指  章鱼哥
You've got to try these mummy fingers, Squidward
可好吃了
So delicious
诺斯费拉图  务必给我一份秘方
Nosferatu, you simply must give me the recipe
我还是加点番茄酱吧
Well, maybe if I put some ketchup on it
番茄酱
Ketchup?
幸好我有备而来
Good thing I came prepared
开加番茄酱了
Ketching up
诺斯费拉图  来点番茄酱
Nosferatu, ketchup?
主人说
The Master says
睡个安稳觉  别让吸血鬼蝙蝠咬了
"Sleep tight and don't let the vampire bats bite"
主人向你们表示晚安
The Master bids you good night
晚安  诺斯费拉图
Good night, Nosferatu
这地方让我毛毛的
This place gives me the creeps
倒也没啥
But so what?
才住一夜
It's only one night
对吧  海绵宝
Right, SpongeB--
忘刷牙了
Forgot to brush my teeth
忘用牙线剔牙了
Forgot to floss
忘洗头了
Forgot to wash my head
忘擦亮眼睛了
Forgot to polish my eyes
能不能给我好好睡觉
Will you go night night time already?
诺斯费拉图
Nosferatu?
你干嘛要从墙里那样探出头来
Why are you sticking out of the wall like that?
诺斯费拉图居然要咬我
I can't believe Nosferatu tried to bite me
他是活生生的吸血鬼
He's a real life v-v-vampire
他要吸光我们的血
He's gonna suck our blood
一定有办法可以逃出古堡
There's got to be a way out of this castle
我来带你们出去
I can show you a way out
史赖皮好困
Slappy sleepy
走这几扇门试试
Let's try these doors
猩猩怪
Gorilla monster
快  走洗衣滑槽
Quick, down the laundry chute
是吸血鬼棺材
It's a vampire's coffin
诺斯费拉图两步舞
Nosferatu two-step
赶紧回神  海绵宝宝
Snap out of it, SpongeBob
万一他咬了我们脖子
What if he bites our necks
或者我鼻子呢
Or my nose?
我知道怎么办
I know what to do
吸血鬼电影主角都会做木桩打吸血鬼
In those vampire movies
they always make wooden stakes
真是好办法
That's a great idea
来
Here
[ stake（木桩）与 steak（牛排）谐音 ]
没牛排酱还会有效吗
Will these even work without steak sauce?
你们不应该来缠扰主人的衣坟
You shouldn't disturb the master's laundry tomb
他发现你们来这  一定会发火的
He would be very cranky if he found you here
而且你们永远不知道他身处何方
and you never know where he might be
他是不是就在我们身后
He's right behind us, isn't he?
不在
Nope
后面没人
Nobody there
没事的
We're fine
求你别吃我们
Please don't eat us
主人不饿
The master is not hungry
他刚刚吃了一顿大餐
He just had a big lunch
他想把你们的邮件还回去
He wanted to return your mail
你可真贴心
Well, how thoughtful of you
谢谢
Thanks
打开看看  章鱼哥
Open it, Squidward
里面有什么
What'd you get?
来看看
Let's see
好啊
Oh, yes
是我按月订购的大蒜
It's my Garlic of the Month Club
等等
Wait
主人只是在耍你们而已
The master is just joshing with you
他可喜欢大蒜了
He loves garlic
如果把灯弄得闪来闪去的不是你
Well, if you're not flicking the lights on and off
会是谁在搞鬼
then who is?
歌剧魅影
Phantom of the Opera
史赖皮的日常
编剧
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
动画总监
指导总监
统筹
监制
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
选我
Pick me
我
Me
选我
Pick me
选
Pick--
选我
pick me
我
Me
埃斯梅拉达
Esmeralda
晚上好
Good evening
快醒醒  主人
Wakey-wakes, Master
一日之计在于每天吸到的第一滴血
The first blood of the day is the most important
主人
Master?
不好了
Oh, no
你鼻子肿得费拉图不堪了
You've got a stuffy Nose-feratu
必须带你去找鱿医生治疗
We have to get you to Dr. Calamari right away
鱿医生
下一位病人
Next patient
你好  鱿医生
Salutations, Dr. Calamari
主人得了特兰西瓦尼亚吸吸症
The master has a case of
the Transylvanian sniff-sniffs
可以治好他吗
Can you help?
感谢你带你主人过来  史赖皮
Thank you for bringing him in, Slappy
我会把过敏原蒸出他鼻子
I'll steam those allergies right out of his schnoz
两小时后回来接他
Come back in two hours und pick him up
我马上回来  主人
I'll be right back, Master
差点忘了
I almost forgot
是的  主人
Yes, Master
我会带来血样与饼干的
I will bring you blood samples und cookies
两小时
Two hours?
两小时要来干什么呢
What am I gonna do for two whole hours?
来随便做做看吧
Let's find out, eh?
裤头村
欢乐游戏厅
全场游戏两毛五
坟头蹦迪
一起来坟头蹦迪
Get ready to prance, prance on your grave
我爱蹦迪
I just love to prance
感觉真是自由奔放
I feel so free and loose
万岁
Hooray
空心球进了
I made a swish
快来喷水赢大奖
Step right up and squirt yourself a prize
水管喷水瓶
好耶
Yeah
赢家出炉了
We have a winner
赢家  赢家
Winner, winner
快来喷水赢大奖
Step right up and squirt yourself a prize
升天去吧  瓶子
Reach for the sky, bottles
快来喷水
Step right up, and squ--
又有赢家出炉了
We have another winner
宠物店
你好  史莉皮
Hello, Slippy
你今晚样子可真是恶心
You look positively disgusting this evening
你自己样子也挺难看  史赖皮
You look pretty horrifying yourself, Slappy
你想买什么呢
What can I get you today?
我要给主人买罐蝙蝠粮和跳蚤项圈
I need a can of bat food and a flea collar for the master
你主人有你的照顾  运气可真是好
That master sure is lucky
to have you looking out for him
一共多少钱  母夜叉
What do I owe you, gruesome?
不用钱  臭嘴
It's on the house, stink lips
我们以后再见吧  亲爱的
Until our eyes cross again, mon cheri
不好意思
Excuse me
这边有蜗牛尿布卖吗
Do you sell snail diapers?
与旧日好友一同野餐  感觉就是好
It is always great to go on a picnic with old friends
墓地
排骨眼先生
Oh, Mr. Ribeye?
排骨眼先生  现在几点了
Mr. Ribeye, do you have the time?
排骨眼先生
1117年生 1198年卒
我得去接主人了
I have to pick up the master
大家再见
See you soon, everyone
不过别太快就见了
but hopefully not too soon
再见
Bye
改天再见  史赖皮
See you later, Slappy
再见
See you
以后再来
Come back soon
诺斯费拉图
Nosferatu
鱿医生  我回来了
Dr. Calamari, I'm back
诺斯费拉图
Nosferatu
你说吧  医生
So tell me, Doctor
主人治好了吗
is the master cured?
已经康复了
All better
每天晚上滴两次滴鼻液
Make sure he takes these nose drops twice a night
谢谢  鱿医生
Thank you, Dr. C
谁是乖吸血鬼
Who was a good vampire?
是的  我当然给你买了
Oh, yes, of course I bought you
你先前在橱窗那边看到过的跳蚤项圈
that flea collar you saw in the window
帅气迷人啊  主人
Very fetching, Master
存进冰箱里等会儿吃
I'll put that in the fridge for later
不用谢我  主人
You don't have to thank me, Master
你是我最好的朋友
You're my best friend
是的  主人
Yes, Master
我们回去吧
Let's go home now
第一个进古堡的
First one to the castle
变又脏又臭绝望大粪坑
is a filthy, stinking cesspool of despair
我像蝙蝠一样遨游天际
I am soaring like a bat
遨游天际
Soaring